A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, RG 5 Program Files, Subgroup: Grant Files (L-Z), Accession 2021:051 FA1790
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Journalism and Media Innovation, 2002-2017; 2
  - Northeastern University - Media Innovation Track (2015-50455), 2012-2015 (Box 34, Folder 435)
  - Northwestern University - Computer Programming Scholarships (2011-0215), 2010-2013 (Box 35, Folder 440)
  - Northwestern University - Knight News Innovation Lab (2010-0295), 2010-2017 (Box 35, Folder 441-442)
  - One Degree - Prototype of One Degree (2013-47670) (Box 36, Folder 454)
    An app to help people discover, track, and share their experiences about social services.
  - Online Journalism Project - Low-Power FM/Local News Sustainability Project (2015-50780), 2015-2016 (Box 36, Folder 457)
  - Online News Association - Challenge Fund for Innovation in Journalism (2016-53096), 2016-2017 (Box 36, Folder 458)
  - Online News Association - Women's Leadership Accelerator (2017-53956) (Box 37, Folder 459)
  - Online News Association - Journalism 360 (2016-53389), 2016-2017 (Box 37, Folder 460)
  - Online News Association - Local Program and Peer-to-Peer Volunteer Network (2015-51329), 2014-2017 (Box 37, Folder 461)
  - Online News Association - Challenge Fund for Innovation in Journalism Education (2014-48945) (Box 37, Folder 462)
  - Online News Association - Annual Conference Sponsorship (2014-49256), 2012-2016 (Box 37, Folder 463)
  - Online News Association - Challenge Fund for Innovation in Journalism Education (2013-47061), 2012-2015 (Box 37, Folder 464)
  - Online Publishers Association - Digital Content Next: Digital Content Start-Up Memberships (2015-50793), 2014-2017 (Box 37, Folder 465)
  - OpenGov Foundation - Project Madison (2013-42896), 2011-2014 (Box 37, Folder 468)
  - OpenGov Foundation - Open Data and Technology (2014-49438), 2012-2015 (Box 37, Folder 469)
  - Open Mind Legacy Project Inc. - PBS/Open Mind, 60th Anniversary Series on Free Press and Democracy (2016-52424), 2014-2017 (Box 38, Folder 471)
  - Open Source Digital Voting Foundation - Election Night Reporting System (2013-46308), 2011-2013 (Box 38, Folder 478)
  - The Paley Center for Media - PALEYIMPACT (2016-52439), 2014-2017 (Box 39, Folder 486)
  - Paul Quinn - Minezy (2014-48427), 2012-2014 (Box 39, Folder 491)
    Data analysis tool to help journalists deduce social relationships, hierarchical structures and topical importance from email archives.
  - PBS MediaShift - CollabMatch (2013-46296), 2011-2013 (Box 39, Folder 493)
  - PBS MediaShift - Idea Lab (2011-0022), 2010-2013 (Box 39, Folder 494)
  - PEN American Center Inc. - Free Speech on Campus Roadshow (2017-53875) (Box 39, Folder 496)
  - PersonalGenomes.org - Open Humans Network (2014-47980), 2012-2016 (Box 40, Folder 508)
  - The Pew Charitable Trusts - Digital Age Project (2013-47496), 2011-2015 (Box 41, Folder 511)
  - Philadelphia Public Interest Information Network, Inc. - DocumentCloud (2017-54048) (Box 43, Folder 532)
  - Philadelphia Public Interest Information Network, Inc. - OpenDataPhilly (2014-48402) (Box 43, Folder 533)
  - Philip Ashlock - Civic Data Standards Study (2013-46395), 2011-2013 (Box 44, Folder 549)
  - Picturebox - The Newspaperman: Gene Roberts and the Golden Age of Newspapers (2014-50079), 2012-2015 (Box 44, Folder 554)
  - Poynter Institute for Media Studies, Inc. - Verifying Fact-Checkers for Facebook (2017-53782) (Box 45, Folder 567)
  - Poynter Institute for Media Studies, Inc. - Sharing the Lessons of Knight-Temple Table Stakes (2016-53193), 2014-2017 (Box 45, Folder 568)
  - Poynter Institute for Media Studies, Inc. - Leadership Academy for Women in Digital Media (2016-53655) (Box 45, Folder 569)
  - Poynter Institute for Media Studies, Inc. - Leadership Academy for Women in Digital Journalism (2015-51642) (Box 45, Folder 570)
  - Poynter Institute for Media Studies, Inc. - NewsU Redesign (2015-51918), 2014-2017 (Box 45, Folder 571)
  - Poynter Institute for Media Studies, Inc. - Newsroom Training Assessment (2014-48714) (Box 45, Folder 572)
  - President-Board of Trustees, Santa Clara College - The Trust Project (2017-53918) (Box 45, Folder 573)
  - President and Fellows of Harvard College - Audience Engagement Beat Reporting (2017-53926), 2016-2017 (Box 45, Folder 574)
  - President and Fellows of Harvard College - 2016 Electoral News Coverage (2016-52922) (Box 46, Folder 579)
  - President and Fellows of Harvard College - Trust in News Initiative: First Draft Partner Network (2016-53694) (Box 46, Folder 582)
  - President and Fellows of Harvard College - Carnegie-Knight Initiative (2014-49384), 2013-2016 (Box 46, Folder 583)
  - President and Fellows of Harvard College - Knight Visiting Nieman Fellows (2014-50206), 2014-2017 (Box 46, Folder 584)
  - President and Fellows of Harvard College - !nstant [Instant] (2013-47655) (Box 46, Folder 585)
    A mobile app designed to verify and provide context to breaking news and social media.
  - Harvard University - Nieman Lab (2012-2064), 2010-2016 (Box 46, Folder 586)
  - Principled Strategies - SafeUseNow [Safe Use Now] (2014-47982), 2012-2014 (Box 46, Folder 587)
  - ProPublica - Audience Engagement Project (2015-50835), 2013-2017 (Box 47, Folder 593)
  - ProPublica - Umbel Analytics Tool (2013-47136), 2010-2013 (Box 47, Folder 594)
  - ProPublica - Intern Economy Kickstarter (2013-47370), 2010-2013 (Box 47, Folder 595)
  - Public Good Software Inc. - Do Public Good Button (2014-49109), 2012-2014 (Box 47, Folder 600)
  - Public Laboratory for Open Technology and Science - Electronic and New Media (2011-0241), 2011-2012 (Box 47, Folder 602)
  - Public Radio International Inc. - PRI UnConvention Transition 2016 (2016-52947) (Box 47, Folder 604)
  - Public Science - Seer (2013-47604), 2012-2013 (Box 47, Folder 606)
  - Radio and Television News Directors Foundation - RTDNA Training: Digital Transformation and Investigative Journalism (2017-54692) (Box 48, Folder 617)
  - Raleigh Public Record, Inc. - DocHive (2013-46297) (Box 48, Folder 619)
    Tool to extract structured data from image-based PDF files.
  - Reframe It, Inc. - Deliberative Polling (2013-47087), 2012-2014 (Box 48, Folder 623)
  - The Regents of the University of California - Investigative Reporting Program at UC Berkeley (2016-53329), 2016-2017 (Box 49, Folder 627)
  - Regents of the University of Michigan - Detroit Journalism Cooperative: Michigan Radio (2016-53464), 2016-2017 (Box 49, Folder 628)
  - Regents of the University of Michigan - Charles R. Eisendrath Symposium (2016-53642) (Box 49, Folder 630)
  - Regents of the University of Michigan - Detroit Journalism Cooperative (2014-50210), 2014-2016 (Box 49, Folder 631)
  - Regents of the University of Michigan, Ann Arbor - Livingston Awards for Young Journalists (2013-46966), 2012-2015 (Box 49, Folder 632)
  - Reporters Committee for Freedom of the Press - Knight Litigation Project (2016-52405), 2014-2017 (Box 49, Folder 633)
  - Reporters Committee for Freedom of the Press - 2016 First Amendment Awards (2016-52821) (Box 49, Folder 636)
  - Robert C. Maynard Institute for Journalism Education - Strategic Plan (2015-50990), 2014-2016 (Box 50, Folder 639)
  - Robert C. Maynard Institute for Journalism Education - Politico Internships (2014-49170) (Box 50, Folder 640)
  - Robert C. Maynard Institute for Journalism Education - Cultural Competency for Journalism Education (2017-54280) (Box 50, Folder 641)
  - Rochester Institute of Technology - Digital Journalism Incubator (2013-47092), 2011-2014 (Box 50, Folder 644)
  - Rutgers University Foundation - Gloria Steinem Endowed Chair in Media, Culture, and Feminist Studies (2017-54386) (Box 51, Folder 652)
  - Salak Telesystem (STS) - Poking the Bear (2014-49111) (Box 51, Folder 662)
    A system to track and inform the public of restricted access to the open internet by mobile operators.
  - School of Journalism and Mass Communication Foundation of North Carolina - Campaign Hound (2015-51044), 2013-2015 (Box 53, Folder 695)
  - School of Journalism and Mass Communication Foundation of North Carolina - Capitol Hound (2014-48415), 2012-2014 (Box 53, Folder 696)
  - School of Journalism and Mass Communication Foundation of North Carolina - Local Information and Rural Newspapers (2011-0238), 2010-2013 (Box 53, Folder 697)
  - Seth Vincent - Flatsheet (2014-50226), 2012-2015 (Box 54, Folder 702)
    A tool to help newsrooms collaboratively curate data in real time.
  - Sigman Delta Chi Foundation - Excellence in Journalism 2016 Conference (2016-52317), 2016-2017 (Box 54, Folder 707)
  - Sociedad Interamericana de Prensa, Inc. - SipConnect (2016-52593), 2014-2017 (Box 56, Folder 728)
  - Sociedad Interamericana de Presna, Inc. - American Press Association's Strategic Plan (2013-43294), 2011-2014 (Box 56, Folder 729)
  - Society for News Design Foundation, Inc. - Digital Design Training (2016-53395), 2016-2017 (Box 56, Folder 730)
  - Society for Science and the Public - Strategic Planning for the Science News Media Group (2016-52656) (Box 56, Folder 731)
  - Solution Beam LLC - Geo Data App (2014-48512), 2012-2014 (Box 56, Folder 733)
  - Solutions Journalism Network - Philadelphia Collaborative Reporting Project (2016-53369), 2016-2017 (Box 56, Folder 734)
  - Solutions Journalism Network, Civic Ventures - Positive Deviance Journalism (2014-47981), 2012-2014 (Box 56, Folder 735)
  - Solutions Journalism Network, Civic Ventures - Solution-Oriented Journalism (2013-47277), 2012-2014 (Box 56, Folder 736)
  - Southern California Public Radio - Project Carbon NPR (2015-51362), 2015-2016 (Box 57, Folder 747)
  - Spark Camp Inc. - Spark Tracks (2014-48577), 2012-2015 (Box 59, Folder 766)
  - Sportsmanias - Social Media and Sports Summit (2015-50395) (Box 59, Folder 767)
  - Stamen Design, LLC - Extending maps.stamen.com (2014-48453), 2012-2014 (Box 59, Folder 771)
  - Stamen Design, LLC - Public Data Visualization Tool, Knight News Challenge (2010-0142), 2010-2012 (Box 59, Folder 772)
  - Stanford University - Knight-Risser Prize for Western Environmental Journalism (2010-0039), 2009-2016 (Box 59, Folder 773)
  - Smart Chicago Collaborative - Foodborne Chicago (2013-47651) (Box 60, Folder 789)
  - Tal Achituv - Public Record (Advanced Emergency Radio Scanner and Repository) (2014-49150) (Box 62, Folder 808)
  - Telepaz, LLC - Keepr (2013-47767), 2012-2014 (Box 63, Folder 837)
    A data mining tool for journalists to track breaking news stories.
  - Temple University - Digital Transformation inside Legacy Newsrooms (2015-51338), 2015-2016 (Box 63, Folder 839)
  - Texas State University, San Marcos - Ph.Digital: Preparing Future Faculty to Lead Innovative Curriculum (2017-54096) (Box 64, Folder 842)
  - Texas Tribune - Kickstarter Project to Livestream the 2014 Texas Election (2014-48120), 2011-2014 (Box 64, Folder 843)
  - Tides Center - Editorial Database (2011-0240), 2009-2014 (Box 65, Folder 854)
    A database for visualizing the relationships among political, civic, and business leaders.
  - Tides Center - Increase Fiscal Literacy (2011-0242), 2009-2012 (Box 65, Folder 855)
    Creation of digital tools to link public spending data to public spending narratives.
  - Tiziano Project - Interactive News Sites, Knight News Challenge (2011-0281), 2011-2012 (Box 65, Folder 860)
    To develop an easy-to-use journalism platform that improves the information flow in communities by combining user-generated content with professional sources to produce visually compelling, interactive news sites.
  - Tribune Publishing Company - The Columbia Daily Tribune, EveryBlock.com (2010-0090) (Box 66, Folder 868)
  - Trustees of Boston University - Public Radio BizLab: Human-Centered Business Model Design (2016-53734) (Box 66, Folder 870)
  - Trustees of Boston University - Project Carbon, NPR (2015-51366), 2013-2016 (Box 66, Folder 871)
  - Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York - The New Gatekeepers (2017-54290) (Box 66, Folder 872)
  - Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York - Pulitzer 2.0 (2015-50847), 2013-2016 (Box 66, Folder 877)
  - Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York - First Amendment Rights in the Digital Age (2015-50960), 2013-2015 (Box 66, Folder 878)
  - Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York - Knight First Amendment Institute (2015-50961), 2012-2017 (Box 67, Folder 879-880)
  - Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York - Punch Sulzberger Executive Leadership Program (2015-51678), 2015-2017 (Box 67, Folder 881)
  - Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York - Data Journalism Degree (2014-49168), 2013-2015 (Box 67, Folder 882)
  - Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York - Tow Center (2014-49899), 2013-2017 (Box 67, Folder 883)
  - Trustees of the University of Pennsylvania - Addressing the Misinformation Ecosystem (2017-53901) (Box 67, Folder 885)
  - Trustees of the University of Pennsylvania - The Media Future Summit (2016-53383) (Box 67, Folder 887)
  - University of Akron Foundation - ICAkron (Informed Citizen Akron) (2015-52015), 2014-2016 (Box 69, Folder 914)
  - University of Arizona - Freedom of Information Landscape Research (2016-53178), 2015-2016 (Box 69, Folder 917)
  - University of California, Berkeley - Hunting Corruption, News21 (2011-0225), 2010-2012 (Box 70, Folder 918)
  - University of Florida Foundation - Journalism Interactive (2016-52094) (Box 70, Folder 921)
  - University of Florida Foundation - The Innovators (2013-47288), 2011-2014 (Box 70, Folder 923)
  - University of Maryland - Journalism Interactive Conference (2017-53859), 2013-2017 (Box 70, Folder 927)
  - University of Miami - Knight Center for International Media (2006-0184), 2006-2008 (Box 72, Folder 944-945)
  - University of Miami - Knight Center for International Media (2006-0184) - World Press Photo, Educational CD-ROM (Box 72, Folder 945)
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
  - University of Miami - Knight Center for International Media (2006-0184) - Somosfoto, Ecuador 2005 (Box 72, Folder 945)
  - University of Michigan, Ann Arbor - Detroit Journalism Cooperative (2013-47626) (Box 72, Folder 946)
  - University of Michigan, Ann Arbor - Livingston Awards for Young Journalists (2012-0211), 2012-2013 (Box 72, Folder 947)
  - University of Mississippi - Nonprofit Journalism (2004-0175), 2004-2005 (Box 73, Folder 948)
  - University of Missouri - "We Live Here" (2015-50692) (Box 73, Folder 949)
    To promote explanatory journalism and community discussions around racial disparities in the St. Louis region to explore storytelling and audience engagement in times of crisis.
  - University of Nebraska Foundation - Mobile Me and You 2 (2016-52745) (Box 73, Folder 950)
  - University of Nebraska Foundation - Drone Vehicles as News and Information Gathering Tools (2012-0103), 2011-2016 (Box 73, Folder 951)
  - University of Nebraska Foundation - Mobile Media Fund (2012-0104), 2010-2016 (Box 73, Folder 952)
  - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - Applied Research Center (2015-50477), 2015-2017 (Box 73, Folder 953)
    Applied research center with a focus on media sustainability and innovative news and digital product solutions.
  - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Arts and Sciences Foundation - W Hodding Carter III Student Fellowship in Public Service (2014-49752), 2014-2015 (Box 73, Folder 954)
  - University of Oregon Foundation - The Communities of Practice Platform for Journalism Community Engagement (2016-52538), 2016-2017 (Box 73, Folder 955)
  - University of Southern California - Annenberg Virtual Reality Journalism Proposal (2016-52470), 2016-2017 (Box 73, Folder 956)
  - University of Texas, Austin - International Symposium on Online Journalism (ISOJ) (2015-51210), 2015-2016 (Box 73, Folder 957)
  - University of Southern California - Mobile Platform (2012-0105), 2010-2015 (Box 73, Folder 958)
  - University of Southern California - Lear Center for Media Metrics (2012-0364), 2012-2016 (Box 74, Folder 959)
  - University of Southern California - Digital Media Center, Knight Community Information Challenge (2011-0356), 2010-2014 (Box 74, Folder 960)
  - University of Southern California - Western Knight Center for Specialized Journalism (2003-0015), 2002-2005 (Box 74, Folder 961-962)
  - University of Texas, Austin - Online Courses (2015-51319), 2013-2017 (Box 74, Folder 966)
  - University Radio Foundation Inc. - NPR One Platform (2017-54046) (Box 75, Folder 974)
  - Ushahidi, Inc. - Curate and Verify Information Mobile App (2011-0243), 2009-2014 (Box 76, Folder 982)
  - Veritza - Prototype (2014-49095), 2012-214 (Box 77, Folder 993)
    A system to aid journalists in the discovery of story leads from public records.
  - VisionWorkshops, Inc. - Photo Camp Cuba (2016-52806), 2015-2016 (Box 77, Folder 1000)
  - Vizzuality, Inc. - Narrative Driven Maps (2013-47630), 2012-2013 (Box 77, Folder 1001)
  - VoiceofSanDiego.org - Memberships (2014-48222), 2012-2015 (Box 77, Folder 1004)
  - Waldo Jaquith - United States Open Data Institute (2013-46962), 2011-2014 (Box 78, Folder 1009)
  - Waldo Jaquith - Platform for Parsing and Displaying State Codes and Legal Decisions (2011-0280), 2011-2012 (Box 78, Folder 1010)
  - Washington Monthly Corporation - Collaboration and Shared Resource Strategy among Legacy Publishers (2017-54218) (Box 78, Folder 1016)
  - Washington Post Company - Fact Check Prototype (2012-0204), 2012-2013 (Box 79, Folder 1017)
  - Wayne State University - Detroit Journalism Cooperative (2013-47625), 2013-2014 (Box 79, Folder 1019)
  - Wayne State University - Detroit Journalism Cooperative: WDET (2016-53463), 2015-2017 (Box 79, Folder 1020)
  - Wesleyan University - Media Project Videos (2014-49010) (Box 79, Folder 1029)
  - WGBH Educational Foundation - Frontline Emblematic VR (2015-51221), 2013-2016 (Box 80, Folder 1033)
  - WHYY, Inc. - PlanPhilly (2017-54035) (Box 80, Folder 1037)
  - WHYY, Inc. - Project Carbon, NPR (2015-51389), 2013-2015 (Box 80, Folder 1038)
  - Wiki Spot - LocalWiki Expansion (2013-42911), 2013-2014 (Box 80, Folder 1040)
  - Wildwood School - Global Sensor Web (2013-47663), 2011-2013 (Box 80, Folder 1041)
  - Will Knight - Facto_Bot (2014-49139), 2012-2014 (Box 80, Folder 1042)
  - Windy Citizen - Real-Time Advertising Software, Knight News Challenge (2010-0143) (Box 81, Folder 1046)
  - WITNESS, Inc. - Mobile App to Verify and Authenticate Media from Mobile Devices (2012-0410), 2011-2013 (Box 81, Folder 1047)
  - The World Press Institute - Whisper Platform (2012-2132), 2010-2012 (Box 82, Folder 1053)
  - World Wide Web Foundation - Tipsy: A Subscription-Microdonation Framework for News Consumers (2014-48526), 2012-2014 (Box 82, Folder 1055)
  - World Wide Workshop for Children's Media Technology and Learning - Digital Media Literacy Program (2011-0293), 2010-2012 (Box 82, Folder 1057)
  - Yale University - Media Freedom and Information Access Clinic (2014-49800), 2014-2017 (Box 82, Folder 1062)
- Arts, 2007-2017; 3
  The Knight Arts program awards grants that promote authenticity and inclusion, development of talent and organizations, and transformation. This series also contains grants that fall under the Knight Arts Challenge in which the grants awarded must focus on the arts, take place in or benefit South Florida, and the awardees much match the amount granted by the Knight Foundation.
  - LBV Films, LLC - Ayiti Images: A Florida Traveling Film Series (2014-50154), 2012-2014 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - League of American Orchestras - National Conference in Detroit (2017-53915), 2014-2017 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lee Ann Etzold - Point Bold: A Neighborhood Project (2012-2273), 2011-2015 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Lincoln Center for Global Exchange (2015-51437), 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Lip Service, Andrea Askowitz - Knight Arts Challenge (2012-0371), 2011-2014 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Project to give a voice to underrepresented Miami stories by coaching underserved members of the community to present a spoken-word performance about their experiences.
  - Little Berlin - Knight Arts Challenge (2012-0082), 2009-2014 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Transform the East Kensington neighborhood by turning an empty lot into an event space for musicians, art fairs, and children's workshops.
  - LiveConnections.org - Collaborative Connections: Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0057), 2009-2012 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Musical programming for underserved audiences.
  - Living Arts Trust, Inc. - Rachelle Salnave and O Cinema, Knight Art Champion Designation (2017-55382) (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Living Arts Trust, Inc. - Charitable Designations, Kareem Tabsch and Vivian Marthell (Reading Queer) (2016-52058) (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Living Arts Trust, Inc. - Charitable Designations, Kareem Tabsch and Vivian Marthell (FilmGate and Miami Moonlighter) (2016-52148) (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Local Projects, LLC - Knight Arts Interactive Museum Platform (2015-50879) (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Locust Projects, LLC - Change by Design: Accelerating Impact at Locust Projects (2017-54798) (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Locust Projects, LLC - Common Field 2016, Miami (2016-52845) (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Locust Projects, LLC - Flat Files and Artist Roundtable (2014-49366), 2011-2016 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Machine Project - Machine Project Playbook (2014-49725) (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Machine Project - Art in Public, Los Angeles (2013-43009), 2010-2013 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Macon Arts Alliance - Birthplace of Macon Documentary Series (2016-52607) (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Macon Arts Alliance - Art Matters: Engaging the Community through Embedded Arts Journalists (2013-45774), 2012-2013 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Macon-Bibb County - Outdoor Film Screening Series (2015-50616) (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Macon Film Festival, Inc. - Virtual Reality Filmmaking Experience (2017-54115) (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Macon Symphony Orchestra - Spencer Meyer (2016-52640) (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Macon Venue Project - Macon Venue Project (2016-52619), 2013-2016 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Crowdsource Symphony Project (2014-49939), 2012-2015 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - McColl Center for Visual Art - Shared Residency, Charlotte Ballet and Javier De Frutos (2017-55037) (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - M Ensemble Company, Inc. - New Play Series, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0352), 2010-2012 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    Forum and mentorship opportunities for African-American playwrights.
  - Miami Art Museum of Dade County Association - Contemporary Art by African-Americans (2013-47456), 2011-2014 (Box 10, Folder 123)
  - Miami Art Museum of Dade County Association - Contemporary Art by African-Americans (2012-0306), 2010-2013 (Box 10, Folder 126)
  - Miami Art Museum of Dade County Association - The Record: Contemporary Art and Vinyl, Knight Arts Challenge (2010-0263), 2010-2012 (Box 10, Folder 127)
  - Miami Bach Society, Inc. - Tropical Baroque Music Festival XVII and "Bach to School" Student Outreach (2015-51659), 2013-2016 (Box 10, Folder 128)
  - Miami Bach Society, Inc. - Bach Festival (2014-49426) (Box 10, Folder 129)
  - Miami Children's Initiative - Liberty City Renaissance (2012-0396), 2012-2014 (Box 10, Folder 132)
  - Miami City Ballet, Inc. - The Nutcracker Costumes and Sets (2017-54638) (Box 10, Folder 133)
  - Miami City Ballet - New Works Fund, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0341), 2008-2012 (Box 10, Folder 135)
  - Miami City Ballet, Inc. - Ana-Marie Codina Barlck, Knight Art Champion Designation (2017-55372) (Box 10, Folder 136)